# **SVETLANA DENISYUK**

## **Frontend Developer**

JavaScript/TypeScript/React/Redux

I am a frontend developer with experience in JavaScript, TypeScript, React, and Redux. Skilled at connecting front-end and back-end systems using RESTful APIs, my problem-solving abilities help me work effectively with design and development teams to create fast and responsive web applications.

**phone:** +972 53 926-01-89

email: svetlana.denisyuk@gmail.com

linkedln: linkedin.com/in/svetlana-denisyuk

**location:** Tel Aviv, Israel

languages: Hebrew-fluent, English-intermediate,

Russian-native

#### **Skills**

Programming languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Java

Frontend Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery, Grid, FlexBox, React Router, React Hooks,

Fetch, Webpack

Backend Technologies: Spring, Spring Boot, RESTful APIs

Frameworks and libraries: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, MUI, Spring Boot, Maven

Databases: MongoDB

IDE/Tools: WebStorm, IntelliJ IDEA, Eclipse, Postman, Firebase, Swagger, GIT

OS: macOS, windows

#### **Work Experience**

#### **2022 – now** Frontend Developer, Elpisor Ltd., Rehovot, Israel

- Built and updated advanced components of our web apps using React, improving performance and scalability
- Integrated Web API services to fetch and display data dynamically on user interfaces, enhancing interactivity and user experience
- Used Redux Toolkit for managing application state, which sped up data retrieval and improved performance

Tools summary: React, Redux/ Redux Toolkit, JavaScript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, GIT

## **2018 - 2019** Frontend Developer, IT Software Solutions, Saint-Petersburg, Russia

- Designed and implemented scalable front-end solutions using HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript for improving user experience
- Developed, refined reusable components, optimizing design processes and application performance
- Managed code upgrades and refactoring, enhancing system performance and maintainability
- Used GIT and GitHub for repo management
- Fixing issues and bugs that arise

Tools summary: React, Redux, JavaScript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, GIT

### Education

2013-2017 Bachelor's degree in Information Technologies

Angarsk State Technical University

2020-2021 Back End Developer Program

Tel-Ran Education Center, Haifa, Israel